Lukasz Pietraszek

Senior Front-end Developer

Personal Details

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/pietraszekl / Twitter: @pietraszekl Website: https://pietraszekl.github.io/

Nationality: Polish

Personal Summary

Senior Front-end developer with proven track-record over six years in creating accessible and user-friendly responsive websites. Self motivated and independent minded, with a keen eye for detail. Specializing in building e-commerce website (B2C and B2B) using SAP Hybris and latest front-end tech stack.

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES6), jQuery, Handlebars, RequireJS, Webpack, Sass, Less, Responsive Web Design, Usability, UX, Vue.js

Tools

SAP Hybris, WordPress, Eclipse, GIT, SVN, Grunt.js, Axure RP, Photoshop, Illustrator

Work Experience

Front-end Developer

September 2016 - present

Envoy Digital // www.envoydigital.com

Working on number of responsive projects:

- Arsenal FC Direct: Implementing monogram solution for shirts utilizing Amplience tools
- Office Shoes: Collect Plus for pickup from store
- Sofa.com: SAP Hybris, AJAX, Vue.js (Fabric picker)
- LK Bennet
- <u>Dreams.co.uk</u> SAP Hybris, ES6, Webpack, AJAX, Handlabars, Amplience Content Authoring, WordPress

Tech stack:

JavaScript (ES6), Vue.js (on Sofa.com), Amplience (monogram and ViewerKit), AJAX, Handlebars, Webpack, Grunt, Less, Git, SAP Hybris

Front-end Developer

March 2016 - August 2016

DigitasLbi Commerce (Sceneric)

My second contract at DigitasLbi Commerce (previously known as Sceneric). Worked on Gucci Asia websites Project website: http://www.gucci.com/

Tech stack:

JavaScript, ¡Query, AJAX, Handlebars, CSS3/Sass, Git, SAP Hybris

Front-end Developer

January 2016 - March 2016

Stella & Dot // www.stelladot.com

Worked on converting static pages to Angular based templates. Collaborating with team in US (San Francisco) in delivering new layouts for European version of the website. Creating custom responsive pages and developing prototypes for marketing team.

Tech stack:

JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, AngularJS, CSS3, Git

Front-end Developer

October 2015 - December 2015

Jack Wills // www.jackwills.com

Maintenance and bug fixing main website as well as creating micro pages using AngularJS.

Tech stack:

GIT, RequireJS, HTML, CSS3, LESS, AngularJS, GSAP, Demandware, Exact Target and Monetate.

Front-end Developer

September 2015 - October 2015

Sceneric // www.sceneric.com

Integrated front-end prototype with SAP Hybris for Gucci's new ecommerce website.

Project website: http://www.gucci.com/us/en

Tech stack:

JavaScript, jQuery, Handlebars, RequireJS, Ajax, HTML, CSS3, HTML5, JSTL, GIT, SAP Hybris

Front-end Developer

August 2015 -September 2015

Jack Wills // www.jackwills.com

Maintenance and bug fixing main website.

Tech stack:

JavaScript, jQuery, Handlebars, RequireJS, HTML5, CSS3/LESS, Demandware

UI Developer

August 2013 – August 2015

Portaltech Reply // portaltechreply.co.uk

Developed and integrated front-end with SAP Hybris for number of e-commerce websites.

Projects: <u>AB</u>, <u>Delhaize</u>, <u>Monsoon/Accessorize</u>, SanMar (B2B project with Angular 1.5), Phones4U, British American Tobacco VEO (B2B project)

Tech stack:

HTML5, CSS3, Less/SASS, Bootstrap 3, jQuery, JavaScript, AJAX, AngularJS, JSTL, SVN, SAP Hybris

Front-end Developer

May 2011 - August 2013

BioMed Central // www.biomedcentral.com

At BioMed Central online publisher of scientific articles I worked as a part of Web Design and User Experience team on designing layouts and front end structure for three main portals and tens of independent journals. I'm also responsible for developing WordPress themes for blogs and conferences websites using responsive web design with HTML5 and CSS3.

Projects: biomedcentral.com/biome, blogs.biomedcentral.com, biomedcentral.com/researchawards, beyond-the-genome.com

Web and Graphic Designer

November 2007 – May 2011

Ascent Ltd

While working for Ascent IT Ltd online retailer I was responsible for designing and maintaining three main websites (www.hueanimation.com, www.hueanimation.

Projects: hueanimation.com, huehd.com, sogatel.com

Front-end Developer

August 2006 - May 2011

Looca

Looca was my own freelance design company. For several years I have created websites for established online businesses, international charities and independent artists

Projects: elenabudnikova.com, voie-du-diamant.org/en/, pureviewarchitects.com

Education & Qualifications

ABC Level 3 Certificate in Digital Graphics

September 2008 - August 2009

London College of Communication, Elephant & Castle, London SE1 6SB

ABC Level 3 Award in Time-Based Web Design

February 2008 – May 2008

London College of Communication, Elephant & Castle, London SE1 6SB

BA Degree in Computer Science in management

September 2002 – June 2005

The University of Management and Marketing, Sosnowiec, Poland

A-Levels (Polish, Mathematics, Geography)

September 1998 – June 2002

Electronics and Informatics High School, Sosnowiec, Poland